If you run it on your phone, your Apple crashed
because of a network got main thread exception. We found
this answer by connecting our device to our computer and
then checking Android device monitor for the error. You can
see here that this is our package name and this
is our process ID. If you search the logs for
that process ID then our error appears. It's triggered ultimately
by a network on main thread exception. If you're curious
as to what line of our code actually caused
this, you can scroll down the stack trace to
read more. This is our framework code that you
can skip and here's where it actually hits our
app. It's within the placeholder fragment class, in the onCreateView method. And
it happens in main activity.java file, in line 116. So
if we go back to the code, on that line you can see that urlConnection.connect
actually caused the error, and that we can't do that on the main thread.